[phone vibrating]
[vibrating stops]
Morning.
Hi.
Yeah.
Sleep okay?
Okay.
Do you remember last night?
Yeah.
I told you
that I hated your guts
and that I never
wanted to see you again.
And then you ran away from me
and hid under a car.
- I did?
- Yeah.
And when we got back home,
you made me
sleep on the floor.
Next to your puke.
I remember that.
Well...
Are you sorry?
[sighs]
For which part?
So do you want to break up?
No.
Well, then...
What's going on?
I don't know, maybe I kind
of hate you right now, Thom...
but that doesn't mean
that I want--
Break up?
Jesus.
Meow for me.
Come on, meow.
[cat meows]
What do you want me to do?
I don't know.
Why does that
have to be up to me?
Why do I have
to decide everything?
♪
'Twas the day before Christmas
and all through the hills,
the reindeer were playing,
enjoying the spills of skating
and coasting,
and climbing the willows...
- So, you seeing him today?
- Yes.
And you're ending things.
For the thousandth time, yes.
Let me see, thanks.
Wow.
"Really hope your friend's okay.
Can't wait to see you today."
Good thing you got your brunch
shift covered, huh, buddy?
How about I text him instead,
and we go watch a movie?
No. That wouldn't be fair.
- To who?
- To Jeremy.
I'm sorry; he has a name?
You've named the fetus
that we're aborting?
Wow!
That transvaginal ultrasound
really worked its magic on you.
He's a person, Cal.
I'm aware, at two months
he's got fingernails,
a heartbeat, a "soul."
It's not his fault.
Thanks.
Okay.
- I love you.
- Yeah.
[phone rings]
Can you come over?
I've been calling you all day.
Just fucking...
come over, okay?
[knocking]
- Hi.
You are shirtless.
You're early.
Come in.
Thanks.
So what movie are we seeing?
Um, I'm really not feeling
a movie right now.
You just wanna
skip straight to drinks?
Yeah, a drink might help.
Help with what?
I'm just...
all over the place.
Found you.
You might wanna leave
your shoes off, actually.
Why's that?
[knocking]
Just a second!
I'm a mess,
I know, and I'm sorry.
It's just been
one of those days,
where the second
I get my makeup on
I just piss it right off,
so you know what I do?
I calm down,
I clean up, I reapply.
Which makes me remember
why I was fucking crying
in the first place,
and then 'thar see blows'
and I just cry all over again--
All I've done today, Cal,
is put on makeup?
Thanks for coming.
Six months!
We've been together
for six months!
Congratulations.
No, it's fucking awful!
Can I use your bathroom?
How old am I, Cal?
I am 25.
People do not get married
when they are 25,
unless they live in Minneapolis.
I do not want
to live in Minneapolis!
- I'm closing the door.
- Don't close the door.
Rude!
So what happened?
Last night, at the
anticlimactic apocalypse party.
You were there.
I was a little preoccupied,
the world was ending.
Ian just proposed, Cal,
marriage, in front of everybody.
What?!
What did you say?
What was I supposed to say?
He had a ring.
Oh, my God, can I see it?
No, I am not
wearing it for chrissake,
I've been dodging him all day!
I don't even know what to do.
Isn't that why you called?
No, actually.
Where's Thom, anyway?
Let's get drunk.
♪
Like, fuck him,
like, seriously fuck him.
Is this straight whiskey?
I'm hungover.
All right.
Can I tell you a secret?
I never liked him anyway.
Not a secret.
I want you to meet
my friend Christopher.
I've met Christopher.
You've not
given him a chance.
You've gotta take him
for a test drive.
We've been together
for four years.
We have a cat.
In gay terms
that's like, 2.8 kids.
I think that's your problem.
- What? The cat?
- Yeah.
No. You're gay, right?
On the weekends.
Yes, you are gay,
gay, gay, gay, gay.
So listen,
this is actually good.
It means that you do not have
to proscribe to all of these,
like, heteronormative standards
and, like, bullshit mores
and puritanical commitments.
It is a little late for that,
don't you think?
Besides, if I give up on this
relationship, Chick-Fil-A wins.
Yeah, but how can you
possibly trust him again?
Maybe I can't.
Maybe that...
just has to be okay.
Wow, love is dead
because you just killed it.
Bang.
Maybe I should get married.
What?
I'm 25,
I'm not getting any younger.
I mean, what if I want to have
kids or something like that?
You hate kids.
Eh, but what if I want them?!
You're gonna hate them.
I'm gonna go break up with Ian.
Maybe you should give yourself
the night to think about it.
That's a terrible idea.
Do ya got any Ambien?
[laughs]
- Thom might?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Let's get it, let's get it.
- Alright.
All right, this time.
This one time.
You sure you're okay
to walk home like this?
Yeah, I do this all the time.
It's really fun for me.
Hey, you sure you don't want
to stay at my place tonight?
I am sure, thank you.
Well, if you need anything
you call me, okay?
I will.
Bye.
I love you.
You're gonna be okay.
Ah...
Fuck.
Yeah.
I'm fucked up.
Me too.
No, I mean I'm fucking...
fucked up.
I'm fucking...
fucked in the head.
Maybe you should ease up
on this stuff for a bit.
I can't do this anymore.
Well, I'm not gonna
peer pressure you.
You don't understand.
No, I don't.
You make me feel, amazing.
You don't hate my guts.
You don't judge me.
No, I don't.
You don't know me.
I'm a piece of shit.
I'm sorry.
I really like you, Jeremy.
But I can't see you anymore.
And that's what
I came here to tell you,
however circuitously.
[sighs]
I'm sorry.
Um, I should go change.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna get dressed outside.
Wait.
It's over, okay?
No, it isn't.
I want to get
to know you, Thom.
Sorry.
[loud humming of lamp]
Kathy?
Hi.
Do you need
some help getting home?
This is my home.
This lamp?
No, this apartment.
Do you want some ice cream?
No, thank you.
You should go home, Thom,
while you still can.
I'll do that.
Thanks.
I was right about you, huh?
[siren wailing in distance]
[door opening]
Hey.
I've gotta tell you something.
What?
I love you.
[crying]
I love you too, asshole.
♪
♪ I'm puttin'
my hopes on you ♪
♪ What a foolish thing
for me to do ♪
♪ Still thinkin'
that you could be ♪
♪ The one for me
and only me... ♪
♪